Edward A. Kane
DC Public Library, Special Collections
Edward A. Kane Papers
1953-1979
DC Public Library, Special Collections
1.75 linear feet; 2 boxes
008
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series 1
  - Federation of Citizens Association newsletter, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Federation of Citizens Association - Health Committee, 1950-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Michigan Park Citizens Association - Constitution, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Michigan Park Citizens Association - Membership list, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Michigan Park Citizens Association - Meeting minutes, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Michigan Park Citizens Association - Newsletters, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Michigan Park Citizens Association - General, 1955-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - National Gateway Citizens Association, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Northeast Council - Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Northeast Council - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Northeast Council - Minutes, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Northeast Council - Newsletter, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Northeast Council - Clippings, 1950-1960 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Northeast Council - General, 1953-1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Woodridge Michigan Park News, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Photograph - Dr. Kane, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 7)